hipipo.com 2016-06-15

# Terms: | HiPipo

---|---  
|    
---  
| 

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads and analytics to our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.hipipo.com/index.php?linkvar=terms>  
PS. On this same page below

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 23/04/2011

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.HiPipo.com  
HiPipo (U) Limited  
P.O Box 22857, Kampala, Uganda  
Plot 371, Block III, Seeta, Mukono  
advertise@hipipo.com  
+256779 345 331, +256712345331  
�  
  
---  
  
## **HiPipo.com Terms of Use Agreement

March  20, 2011

**

HiPipo.com **Pronunced as "Hi Pipo ")** is an online community that connects people through a network of friends and friends of friends. HiPipo is committed to enabling friends and friends of friends. share information and photos about weddings, events, stories, jobs and tour/travel. Members and artist groups can upload music. HiPipo shop is intended to bring buyers and sellers of Automobiles, High Tech Equipment and Real Estate together. Singles can find perfect dates through hipipo. All this on top of a friends emailing system. 

Whether you are a "Visitor" or you are a "Member" , By using the HiPipo Services, you agree to be bound by this Agreement which HiPipo.com may modify from time to time . The term "User" refers to a Visitor or a Member. 

Please choose carefully the information you post and share on HiPipo.com . Your HiPipo.com profile may not include the following any photographs containing nudity, or obscene, excessively violent, harassing, sexually explicit If you become aware of misuse of the HiPipo Services by any person, please contact [HiPipo](http://www.hipipo.com/index.php?linkvar=contact_us).

HiPipo.com reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to reject, refuse to post or remove any posting , or to restrict, suspend, or terminate your access to all or any part of the HiPipo Services at any time, for any or no reason, with or without prior notice, and without liability.

  1. Above 13 years of age for all users and above 18 year of age for users of the dating service 
  2. You acknowledge that HiPipo.com reserves the right to charge for the HiPipo Services 
  3. HiPipo.com may delete any Content that in the sole judgment violates this Agreement or which may be offensive, illegal or violate the rights, harm, or threaten the safety of any person. 
  4. Exploits people in a sexual or violent manner; 
  5. contains nudity, violence, or offensive subject matter or contains a link to an adult website; 
  6. solicits personal information from anyone under 18; 
  7. Provides any telephone numbers, street addresses, last names, URLs or email addresses; 
  8. Promotes information that you know is false or misleading or promotes illegal activities or conduct that is abusive, threatening, obscene, defamatory or libelous; 
  9. Involves commercial activities and/or sales without our prior written consent 
  10. Includes a photograph of another person that you have posted without that person's consent; or 
  11. For artists profiles, uses sexually suggestive imagery or any other unfair, misleading or deceptive Content intended to draw traffic to the profile. 

Please contact us at. with any questions regarding this Agreement.

I HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT AND AGREE TO ALL OF THE PROVISIONS CONTAINED ABOVE.
